Guide to the Robert D. Miller papers, [ca. 1933-1998]
Miller, Robert D. papers
- Series X. World War II Materials
  - CDs of photographs related to WWII, 1423-1425 (Box 5)
Rossiter, S. Caleb. The Chimes of Freedom Flashing. Washington, DC.: TCA Press, 1996
Alexis Lawrence Romanoff. The University Campus. Ithaca, NY: The Cayuga Press, 1960, Inscribed by the author to the Miller family with laid in Romanoff business card and verse written for the Cornell Centennial.
Books Removed From Collection
The 1902 Cornellian the Book of the Junior Class. Cornell University, 1901